Frank Ormsby papers, circa 1967-2004
Emory University
- The Honest Ulsterman literary materials, 1967-1990, Series 2; Boxes 5-16; OP 1 - 5
  - The Honest Ulsterman author files, 1968-1996, Subseries 2.2; Boxes 7-12; OP1-3
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “Choice,” TS (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “The Confinement,” TS (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “The Cup,” TS (Box 10, Folder 38)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “The Fire Tower,” TS (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “Fossils,” TS (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “Friday,” TS (Box 10, Folder 41)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “The Garden Gnome,” TS (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “The Half-Word,” TS (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “The House,” TS (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “Kells,” TS (Box 10, Folder 45)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “Partly Dedicated to a House,” TS (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “Petite Maison,” TS (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “The Return of Helen,” TS (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “Sea or Sky?” TS (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “Shaferi,” TS (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Medbh, Poetry: “The Show House,” TS (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “The Sofa,” TS (Box 10, Folder 52)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “Studies,” TS (Box 10, Folder 53)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “Tobacco Hole,” TS (Box 10, Folder 54)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: “Truganini,” TS (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: "Up the River," TS (Box 10, Folder 56)
    - McGuckian, Medbh, Poetry: "Waterford," TS (Box 10, Folder 57)
    - Montague, John, Correspondence, 1969-1988 (Box 10, Folder 58)
    - Montague, John, Correspondence, announcements and invitations (Box 10, Folder 59)
    - Montague, John, Poetry: "Coldness," "The Massacre," "Northern Express," TS (Box 10, Folder 60)
    - Montague, John, Poetry: "Craigavon Blues," TS (Box 10, Folder 61)
    - Montague, John, Poetry: "A Frenchman in Derry," TS (Box 10, Folder 62)
    - Montague, John, Poetry: "Wedge," TS (Box 10, Folder 63)
    - Montague, John, Poetry: "Weeds," TS (Box 10, Folder 64)
    - Montague, John, Printed material: "Old Mythologies," poem on postcard with MS message from Montague, undated (Box 10, Folder 65)
    - Montague, John, Printed material: "Omagh Hospital," poem in the Poetry Book Society Bulletin (Box 10, Folder 66)
    - Montague, John, Printed material: Review of Montague's A Chosen Light [by Dan Covy?] (Box 10, Folder 67)
    - Montague, John, Photographs (Box 10, Folder 68)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Correspondence, 1970-1976 (Box 10, Folder 69)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Correspondence, 1980-1991 (Box 10, Folder 70)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Correspondence, undated (Box 10, Folder 71)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Poetry: Belfast Group worksheets, undated [incomplete worksheet includes: The Electric Orchard, Grass Window, The Indians on Alcatraz] (Box 10, Folder 72)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Poetry: Belfast Group worksheets, 25 October 1971 [includes: Blowing Eggs, The Radio Horse, The Field Hospital, On a Dog of Unlike Eyes, The Lost Tribe, The Upriver Incident, Party Piece] (Box 10, Folder 73)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Poetry: Knowing My Place, TS mock-up of pamphlet, 1971 [includes: "Rodgers at Loughgall," "Seanchas," "Macha," "Clonfeacle," "Dancers at the Moy," "Belfast," "The Indians on Alcatraz," "Dixon on Tory," "Little Skellig," "Derryscollop," "Leaving the Island"] (Box 10, Folder 74)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Poetry: Spirit of Dawn, TS for pamphlet, 1975 [includes: "Ned Skinner," "Spirit of Dawn," "Cheesecake," "The Mixed Marriage," "Ma," "Keen," "Vaquero," "The Rucksack," "Big Liz," "Largesse," "At Martha’s Deli," "The Big House"] (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Poetry: Spirit of Dawn, mock-up for pamphlet, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 76)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Poetry: Spirit of Dawn, mock-up for pamphlet, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 77)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Poetry: "Centre Piece," MS (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Poetry: "The Glass Boat," TS (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Poetry: "James Dixon The First Tractor That Ever Came to Tory," TS (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Poetry: "The Pink Tandem," TS (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Poetry: "Poem for Lawrence," MS (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Poetry: "Rapunzel," TS (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Poetry: "Taking the Rust," MS (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Poetry: "Uncle Pat," TS (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Prose: "Winners," TS review of Under the Moon, Over the Stars by Michael Longley (Box 10, Folder 86)
    - Muldoon, Paul, Prose: untitled, MS review of No Continuing City by Michael Longley (Box 10, Folder 87)
    - O’Brien, Sean, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - O’Brien, Sean, Correspondence, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Paulin, Tom, Correspondence, 1973-1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Paulin, Tom, Correspondence, undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "Ballywaire," TS (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "The College Record," TS (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "A Desert Development," TS (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "The Editorial Manse," TS (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "From," TS (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "A Kind of Local," TS (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "Image," TS (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "In Antrim," TS (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "No More Photographs," TS (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "Practical Values," TS (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "A Pre-War Arrival," TS (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "Reminders," TS (Box 11, Folder 16)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "A September Rising," TS (Box 11, Folder 17)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "The wind in pine forests, dry twigs…," TS (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - Paulin, Tom, Poetry: "Without Mercy," TS (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - Paulin, Tom, Printed material: "Tom Paulin writes…" in the Poetry Book Society Bulletin, spring 1977 (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - Peskett, William, Correspondence, 1970-1979 (Box 11, Folder 21)
    - Peskett, William, Correspondence, undated (Box 11, Folder 22)
    - Peskett, William, Correspondence, 1969-1970 [to James Simmons] (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - Peskett, William, Poetry: "Cleaning Stables," TS (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - Peskett, William, Poetry: "Window Dressing," TS (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - Price, Victor, Correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - Price, Victor, Poetry: "Commuters" and "Photograph of a Leopard Lady," TS (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Price, Victor, Poetry: "Errant Valkyrie," TS (Box 11, Folder 28)
    - Price, Victor, Poetry: "Georgie," TS (Box 11, Folder 29)
    - Price, Victor, Poetry: "Not Dead Yet," TS (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Price, Victor, Poetry: "Reading to Music," TS (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Price, Victor, Poetry: "Twisted Nerve," TS (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Price, Victor, Prose: "Richard Rowley - A Forgotten Poet," TS [essay] (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Price, Victor, Poetry: A Winning Line, TS [novel] (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Raine, Craig, Correspondence, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Rumens, Carol, Correspondence, 1976-1984 (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Rumens, Carol, Correspondence, undated (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Rumens, Carol, Poetry: A Necklace of Mirrors, TS [includes: ALS from Rumens 24 October 1978 and poems: "Portrait of the Poet as a Little Girl," "Sappho," "Li Ju-Chen’s Dream," "The Witch’s Manuscript," "Song for Puberty," Charlotte's Journey," "The Cruel Mother: A New Version," "The Housewife's Manuscript," "Sylvia Plath: A Dramatic Monologue," "Last Words of the Cumaean Sybil," "Akhmatova in Leningrad," "For the Pioneers," TS] (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Rumens, Carol, Poetry: "Fear," TS (Box 11, Folder 39)
    - Rumens, Carol, Poetry: "The Girl in the Cathedral," TS (Box 11, Folder 40)
    - Rumens, Carol, Poetry: "A Poor Man" and "Small Views," TS (Box 11, Folder 41)
    - Rumens, Carol, Poetry: "Unplayed Music," TS (Box 11, Folder 42)
    - Simmons, James, Correspondence, 1968-1974 (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Simmons, James, Correspondence, 1975-1984 (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Simmons, James, Correspondence, 1988-1996 (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Simmons, James, Correspondence, undated (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Simmons, James, Correspondence, The Poets' House organizational materials (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Simmons, James, Correspondence, The Poets' House promotional materials (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Simmons, Jamess, Poetry: the Belfast Group worksheets, Monday March 1, 1971 [includes: Marital Sonnets, Elegy for J.F. Kennedy, The Publican, A Man of Principle, No Land is Waste, TS] (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: The Poets' House, "Poems in Honor of James Simmons's 60th Birthday," 14 Februrary 1993 [includes: McGuckian's "The Tomorrow Club," Montague's "Last Journey," Ormsby's "Some of Us Stayed Forever," Simmons's "The Island Again," TS] (Box 11, Folder 50)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "The Ballad of Bertrand Russell," TS (Box 11, Folder 51)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "The Cattle Rustling at Cooley," TS (Box 11, Folder 52)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "The Circumnavigators," TS [See also Subseries 1.1: Honest Ulsterman correspondence, letter from Simmons, 22 September 1971] (Box 11, Folder 53)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "The Cook's Song," TS [See also Subseries 1.1: Honest Ulsterman correspondence, letter from Simmons, 22 September 1971] (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "A Customer of Beauty / A Barren Exercise," TS (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Divorce," TS [See also Subseries 1.1: Honest Ulsterman correspondence, letter from Simmons, 22 September 1971] (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Dunlewey: 1977," TS (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Elegy," TS (Box 11, Folder 58)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Escape," TS (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Extempore Effusion on a Hurt Thumb," TS (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Fragments," and "Wish Fulfillment," TS [See also Subseries 1.1: Honest Ulsterman correspondence, letter from Simmons, 22 September 1971] (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "The Heart of his Mystery: Derek Mahon Reads his Poetry," TS (Box 11, Folder 62)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Holiday in Garvagh," TS [See also Subseries 1.1: Honest Ulsterman correspondence, letter from Simmons, 22 September 1971] (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "J.M. Synge," TS (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Leeds. 1958," TS (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "The Liberator," TS (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "The Man Outside the Beauty Parlour," TS (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Marital Sonnets," TS (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Nancy With the Laughing Face," TS [See also Subseries 1.1: Honest Ulsterman correspondence, letter from Simmons, 22 September 1971] (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "To One Watching With Envy a Game of Tennis Played by Experts," TS (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "On Secondment," TS [See also Subseries 1.1: Honest Ulsterman correspondence, letter from Simmons, 22 September 1971] (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Second Settler's Soliloquy," TS [See also Subseries 1.1: Honest Ulsterman correspondence, letter from Simmons, 22 September 1971] (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Set Peace," TS [See also Subseries 1.1: Honest Ulsterman correspondence, letter from Simmons, 22 September 1971] (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Sex, Rectitude and Loneliness," TS (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "The Straight Line and the Circle," TS (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Strip to Essentials," TS [See also Subseries 1.1: Honest Ulsterman correspondence, letter from Simmons, 22 September 1971] (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "The Strong Breed," TS (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "The Troubles," TS (Box 12, Folder 16)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Twenty Years," TS (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Valediction to the Editors," TS (Box 12, Folder 18)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "When She's Late Home," TS (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "White Gloves Across the Border," TS (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "Why to the Wilderness," TS [See also Subseries 1.1: Honest Ulsterman correspondence, letter from Simmons, 22 September 1971] (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: "The Wreckers," TS [See also Subseries 1.1: Honest Ulsterman correspondence, letter from Simmons, 22 September 1971] (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - Simmons, James, Poetry: untitled (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - Simmons, James, Prose: A Boyhood in the Colony, TS autobiography [includes chapters 5 ("Mother and Garden") and 7 ("'Training,' an Interlude")] (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Simmons, James, Prose: "Author's Note," TS [autobiographical sketch] (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Simmons, James, Prose: "Art and Politics," TS [essay] (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Simmons, James, Prose: "Dr. Conrad," TS [essay] (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Simmons, James, Prose: "Huckleberry Finn (1), (2)," TS [essays for The Honest Ulsterman's "The Entertainment Section"] (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Simmons, James, Prose: "The Thoughts of Derek Montgomery," TS [essays] (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Simmons, James, Prose: "The Thoughts of Derek Montgomery," proofs [essays include: "James Joyce," "Understanding," "Religion as Literature"] (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Simmons, James, Prose: untitled, TS review of The Big Chapel by Thomas Kilroy (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - Simmons, James, Prose: untitled, TS review of Fergus by Brian Moore (Box 12, Folder 32)
    - Simmons, James, Prose: untitled, TS review of A Man Flourishing by Sam Hanna Bell (Box 12, Folder 33)
    - Simmons, James, Printed material: Programs [including The Cattle Rustling] (Box 12, Folder 34)
    - Simmons, James, Printed material: Reviews of James Simmons (Box 12, Folder 35)
    - Simmons, James, Artwork (Box 12, Folder 36)
    - Sumner, Piotr, Correspondence: 1976-1984 (Box 12, Folder 37)
    - Waterman, Andrew, Correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 12, Folder 38)
    - Waterman, Andrew, Poetry: "Summer Truce," TS (Box 12, Folder 39)
    - Williams, Patrick, Correspondence, 1975-1981 (Box 12, Folder 40)
    - Williams, Patrick, Correspondence, undated (Box 12, Folder 41)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Abuse by Fire," "Getting Home," "God & Angels," "God Talk," "Mountain," "Murphy," "Poor Old Death," TS [collected as a group] (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Alma Mater," "Boozed," "The Boys," "Carnival," "For Those Concerned," "In the Pen," "The Salt Town," "Seize the Day," "Vampire," "A Warning," "Winter," TS [collected as a group] (Box 12, Folder 43)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Certain Gardens," "A Choice," "A Glance Behind," "In the Room," "On a Clear Day," "Sick Joke," "Shock Treatment," "Ten Years," TS [collected as a group] (Box 12, Folder 44)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "The Ghost Houses," "Here Comes Everybody," "Midnight Mass," "Progress Report," "Speech Surgery," TS [collected as a group] (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Caller," TS (Box 12, Folder 46)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Children of Ice," TS (Box 12, Folder 47)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "The Curator," TS (Box 12, Folder 48)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Exhumation," TS (Box 12, Folder 49)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Getting Home," TS (Box 12, Folder 50)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Little Job," TS (Box 12, Folder 51)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Murphy," TS (Box 12, Folder 52)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "New Year Encyclical," TS (Box 12, Folder 53)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Light," TS (Box 12, Folder 54)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "A Personal Matter," TS (Box 12, Folder 55)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Place," TS (Box 12, Folder 56)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Poem," TS (Box 12, Folder 57)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Shelter," TS (Box 12, Folder 58)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Speech Surgery," TS (Box 12, Folder 59)
    - Williams, Patrick, Poetry: "Ten Years," TS (Box 12, Folder 60)
    - Young, Augustus, Correspondence, 1970-1974, includes undated correspondence (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Young, Augustus, Poetry: "Ballad of Fat Margot," TS (Box 12, Folder 62)
    - Young, Augustus, Poetry: "Going to the City," TS (Box 12, Folder 63)
    - Young, Augustus, Poetry: "Skirtings," TS (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Submissions to The Honest Ulsterman, circa 1968-1989, Subseries 2.3; Boxes 13-14
    This subseries consists of The Honest Ulsterman submissions from the late 1960's to the late 1980's by writers not included in Ormsby's author files. Materials in subsections related to poetry, prose, and artwork are arranged by author. These manuscript and typescript drafts do not include information about whether or not they were accepted for publication; nor do they include many editorial remarks by Ormsby.
    Arranged alphabetically by author.
    - Poetry
    - Beresford, Richard and Vanja Karas (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Brennan, Rory (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Clifton, Harry (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Cumberlege, Marcus (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Daly, Padraig J. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Deane, John F. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Denman, Peter (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Duggan, Matt (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Eckhard, Priscilla (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Fiacc, Padraig (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Flanagan, Robert (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Forbes, Duncan (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Fulton, Robin (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Galligan, Frank (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Garfitt, Roger (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - Gorman, Damian (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - Gorman, Michael (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - Gurney, John (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Hamilton, Robin (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Henson, Stuart (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Hughes, Glyn (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Hughes, John (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Jamie, Kathleen (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Johnston, Fred (Box 13, Folder 24)
    - Keller, David (Box 13, Folder 25)
    - Kelly, Michael (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - King, Patrick (Box 13, Folder 27)
    - Latham, John (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Lavery, Leo (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Longley, Edna (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Lopez, Noreen (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - MacCaig, Norman (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Magee, Wes (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - MacMullen, Maol (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Markham, E. A. (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - McCabe, Brian (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - McCracken, Kathleen (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - McDonald, Peter (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - McKinnon, William (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - McLaughlin, Tom (Box 13, Folder 40)
    - McWhirter, George (Box 13, Folder 41)
    - Milne, Ewart (Box 13, Folder 42)
    - Murphy, Hayden (Box 13, Folder 43)
    - Murphy, Liam (Box 13, Folder 44)
    - O'Loughlin, Michael (Box 13, Folder 45)
    - O'Sullivan, D. J. (Box 13, Folder 46)
    - Peacock, Alan (Box 13, Folder 47)
    - Porter, Peter (Box 13, Folder 48)
    - Quinn, Patrick J. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Rae, Simon (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Robinson, Geoffrey (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Scammell, William (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Scully, Maurice (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Shanahan, Deirdre (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Smyth, Damian (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Smyth, Gerard (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Squires, Geoffrey (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Stephens, Michael (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Sweeney, Matthew (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Turner, W. Price (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Weir, Anthony (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Weir, Anthony [poems and prints or related artwork] (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Wheeler, Marcus (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Wilger, Robert (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Young, Augustus (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Anonymous poetry (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - Prose
    - Harris, Jason [drama] (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - Hogan, Desmond (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Hood, R. P. H. (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Ireland, Denis (Box 14, Folder 22)
    - Kane, John (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Kelly, Michael (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - MacLeod, George (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - McBratney, Sam (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - McClelland, Colin (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - McLaughlin, Tom (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - McMahon, Arthur (Box 14, Folder 29)
    - Molloy, John P. (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - Morrow, John (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Weir, Anthony (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - Anonymous prose (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Artwork
    - Anonymous artist's drawing (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Ulsterman Publications, Subseries 2.4; Box 15-Box 16: folders 1-3; OP4
    This subseries contains materials relevant to various projects or texts produced by Ulsterman Publications. As a small publishing operation in its own right, Ulsterman Publications produced The Honest Ulsterman as well as pamphlets or chapbooks for numerous younger poets. Subsections include typescripts and galley proofs of cover art for various pamphlets. Similarly, other subsections contain typescript mock-ups for two editions of The Honest Ulsterman and cover art for several other numbers of the magazine.
    - Ulsterman Publications pamphlets
    - Carson, Ciaran, The Lost Explorer, TS (1978) (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Ormsby, Frank, Being Walked by a Dog, TS (1979) (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Paulin, Tom, Personal Column, TS (1979) [unpublished] (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Peskett, William, A Killing in the Grove, TS (1977) (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Ulsterman Publications pamphlets, cover art
    - Ewart, Gavin, An Imaginary Love Affair [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Johnstone, Robert, Our Lives Are Swiss [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - King, Patrick, Still Running [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Mahon, Derek, Light Music [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Marshall, Douglas, Upstairs Neighbours, [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Peskett, William, Cleaning Stables [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Peskett, William, A Killing in the Grove [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Smith, Ian Crichton, Poems for Donalda [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - List of pamphlets 1969-1971 (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - The Honest Ulsterman selected editions
    - The Honest Ulsterman, number 73 [TS mock-up of Louis MacNeice supplement] (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - The Honest Ulsterman, number 85 [TS mock-up] (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - The Honest Ulsterman selected editions, cover art
    - The Honest Ulsterman, number 51 [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - The Honest Ulsterman, number 52 [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - The Honest Ulsterman, number 53 [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - The Honest Ulsterman, number 54 [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - The Honest Ulsterman, number 55 [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - The Honest Ulsterman, number 61 [cover art proofs] (Box OP4)
    - The Honest Ulsterman, unknown number [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - The Honest Ulsterman, unknown number [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - The Honest Ulsterman, unknown number [cover art proofs] (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - The Honest Ulsterman miscellaneous materials
    - The Honest Ulsterman, original subscription book for numbers 1-82 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Summary of contents, The Honest Ulsterman, numbers 1-78 (Box 15, Folder 25)